<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">WOP TheoApp</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Mission">
     A humble servant God with unmistable marks of
apostleship upon him.Professor E.H Guti  holds
D.D and D.Min and PhD in religion.He is the founder
of the largest and fastest growing Pentecostal Church
in Southern and Central region of Africa.He has been
preaching for nearly seven Decades.God has used him to
raise thousands of churches around the globe.he overseas
several thousands of pastors and evangelists.Apostle Guti
has established several bible schools in Zimbabwe,Mozambique,
RSA,Zambia,Ghana and  the UK where students are trained for
Full time ministry.In addition,he has hundreds of evening and
inline Bible around the world where lay leaders are equipped
to do the work of the ministry.Professor E.H Guti has founded
many ministries that serve specific areas in the lives of God\'s
people these include Africa Christian Business Fellowship(ACBF)
,Gracious Women and Husbands Agape(GWAHAFI),FIF Children\'s Homes
,Ministry to the blind,Ministry to the disabled and Forward in
Faith College and High School Ministry to name just a few.He has
built the Zimbabwe Ezekiel Guti University(ZEGU) in pursuit to
the development of a total man inside and out while spreading
Christian morals in society,the Mbuya Dorcas Hospital,addition
Healing and Deliverance centre and a 24hours Television station
Ezekiel TV.He has authored over 100 books.Professor Ezekiel Guti
established churches in 128 nations and states on every continent.
He is used mightily as a prophet whose wisdom and insight is sought
after by people from all walks of life,from politicians to ordinary
citizens,captains of industry to workers,church leaders to church
members and marriage counseling.It is through his many years of experience
as a counselor that he says &quot;people are people&quot; and his burden is to
see the standard of people raised as they operate in the kingdom of God
.As an evangelist mighty miracles have characterized his ministry for 68years.He
 is a man of love,a passionate soulwinner,a fervent intercessor and 
has a great fatherly heart   
    </string>
    <string name="arch">ARCH BISHOP</string>
</resources>